A Boy Scout at the affiliated level showed off his speaking skills in Indonesia.
Warm red pants, some crabs, if the style is good, it would be Good
Morning Mist Alina and thank you
would, this is good, by the sea, you and
the sea of
fog,
Of War Vietnam, 150 years, yes,
of both, Banking number one
Auto,
full amount, time to return, next day, take it,
zx10, least, not only does via
infrared
u&v in file to Beach View, So, as far as the
time is, with speed, you the Beer
nontawat Challenge U Bolt because
Indonesia is a damn water, but I want to speak, watch.
Han cotton threads were born and furnished
in your Child Is One southern and the
only one. What is Still full? There's
Serena Zhang, Teng Ruz Lee and D. by you
need to have Big. Grandma Te
Daze bba Tu amor. This is the day.
We Down using the Hand. If
you when
will Make Up Feat Sin Hey. And Say
The Philippines Indonesia
and Review the day. Without You
Think Out. Hand but morning.
We like to share the Beast.
Remember Last Year. The PC? Yes,
it left. Got The Ice Bucket Challenge they
use. We want to the end this.
Soul of a friend in diversity.
Lead The Win This Year. The Best is
a Malaysian. Teammin is Leonis will
have the Mix is ​​Just A
definite. Name you say Number One. And
They Have is the day. We Down
using the Hand. Indonesia, Philippines,
Vietnam and TMB Set and Corporate
and Win this contract.
Lesbean andis in the market.
Vietnam Will Be The Winner. We will
Give You So Good Luck.
Indonesia and the Falcon from
Vietnam. With Love stars. Let's leave the stars.
Indonesia. The
bottom part will be...